<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JavaScript on Cynthia&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://cynthiakar.github.io/languages/javascript/</link>
    <description>Recent content in JavaScript on Cynthia&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 18:19:34 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cynthiakar.github.io/languages/javascript/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>recipE-Z</title>
      <link>https://cynthiakar.github.io/posts/recipez/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 18:19:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cynthiakar.github.io/posts/recipez/</guid>
      <description>recipE-Z: the recipe finder app January - May 2020
What is recipE-Z? As a way to help alleviate food waste, we built an iOS app that will present you with recipes based on the ingredients you already have. A user can enter a list of ingredients or a specific recipe and then our app will search through a database of recipes, from online or submitted by users in our app. It will present results ranging from recipes that can be made with everything the user already has to recipes that will require extra ingredients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>divvi</title>
      <link>https://cynthiakar.github.io/posts/divvi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 18:20:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cynthiakar.github.io/posts/divvi/</guid>
      <description>divvi: the bill splitting app February 2020
In February, I participated in my second hack-a-thon, CuseHacks, and our team won Best Use of Google API!
What is divvi? We built a receipt scanner app called &amp;lsquo;divvi&amp;rsquo; that focused on facilitating a productive conversation between you and your fellow meal splitters by itemizing your receipt and calculating the totals owed by each. We prioritized the user experience and wanted to promote chatter at the table rather than detract from it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resumate</title>
      <link>https://cynthiakar.github.io/posts/resumate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 14:14:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cynthiakar.github.io/posts/resumate/</guid>
      <description>Markdown is fully supported So are a variety of other flavors If you prefer certain flavors, you should check it out on the official documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>